孩子们看了无数遍
They've watched it a thousand times.
台词都能倒背如流
They can quote every line.
今年在他们心里
As far as your kids are concerned,
最爱的电影就是...
the only movie that matters this award season is...
是《K-Pop: 猎魔女团...
KPop Demon --
是《一战再战》！
One Battle After Another!
现在就买美泰公司《一战再战》角色玩偶
Now bring the battle home with "One Battle After Another"
《一战再战》角色玩偶
在家重温每场激战
action figures from Mattel.
《一战再战》角色玩偶
美泰出品
是叛娅·富山！
Perfidia Beverly Hills!
孩子们 欢迎加入革命
Welcome to the revolution, kids.
一起去打恶魔吧
Now fight them demons.
太酷了
Awesome!
出自备受好评的保罗·托马斯·安德森
All your favorite heroes and villains from Paul Thomas Anderson's
《一战再战》角色玩偶
美泰出品
抗击种族暴政的杰作
critically lauded masterpiece about resistance in the face of racial tyranny
片中所有英雄和反派 现在尽在你掌中
now in the palm of your hands.
太棒了
Yeah!
有穿战袍的鲍勃·弗格森
Like Battle Robe Bob Ferguson,
穿战袍的
鲍勃·弗格森
配有可发光的奇妙小卷和寻亲配对器
with light-up joint and little homing device.
“我嗨翻了”
I'm so high!
瑟吉奥大师 带有网红级喝酒桥段
Sensei Sergio, with real beer-chugging action.
柔道大师
瑟吉奥
“就喝了点小啤酒”
I had a few small beers.
还包括各种你爱的革命角色
Collect all your favorite revolutionaries.
还包括各种
你爱的革命角色
你好呀
Oh, hello!
你叫什么啊？
What's your name?
“我叫贱女姜戈”
My name is Junglepussy.
贝卡 你怎么能说这种话！
Becka Lee!
“看清楚了吗？这就是黑人力量的化身”
See my face? This is what black power looks like.
别忘了还有叛娅·富山
And don't forget about Perfidia Beverly Hills,
叛娅·富山
带有可拆卸的孕妇肚和机关枪
with snap-on pregnant belly and machine gun.
“吃枪子吧 蠢猪男人”砰 砰 砰...
Take that, pig!
小心 紧随其后的是又傻又壮的勒喉乔上校
But look out. Hot on their trail is the buff, weird Colonel Lockjaw,
勒喉乔上校
配有逼真肌肉血管和现场亲子鉴定仪
with realistic arm veins and mobile paternity testing kit.
“绝不允许失败”
Failure is not an option.
遵命 长官
Okay. Yes, sir!
“你喜欢黑妞吗？”
Do you like black girls?
- 什么？ - “我爱死她们了”
- What? - 'Cause I love 'em.
“爱死她们了！”
I love 'em!
还可购买《一战再战》场景小屋把你的战斗体验升级
Plus, take your battles to the next level with "One Battle After Another" playsets,
瑟吉奥公寓 银行 春歧途酒店
比如瑟吉奥大师的公寓
like Sensei Sergio's apartment,
瑟吉奥大师的公寓
配有真正的暗门 帮你的拉丁裔朋友逃跑
with real working trapdoor to help your Latino friends escape,
或在昏暗的汽车旅馆里
or make one moral sacrifice after another
春歧途酒店
上演一炮再一炮的道德牺牲
in the dimly lit motel room.
不行 别学这个桥段
Nope, we're not doing that scene. Okay.
选好你的载具 开上路继续战斗
Take the battle on the road with the deluxe vehicles.
比如鲍勃那辆破车
Like Bob's crappy car,
开在沙漠路上 尽享50次人生起伏
Or 50-piece desert road with so many rolling hills.
沙漠路拼装 50片
尽享人生起伏
现在就买美泰公司《一战再战》
"One Battle After Another" action figures,
《一战再战》角色玩偶 载具 场景小屋
角色玩偶 载具和场景小屋
vehicles, and playsets from Mattel.
《一战再战》角色玩偶 载具 场景小屋
美泰出品
还有保罗·托马斯·安德森的更多杰作可供选择
Part of the Paul Thomas Anderson master set.
《私恋失调》
《木兰花》
《不羁夜》
“我抛下了我的孩子”
I've abandoned my child!
【译注：出自《血色将至》】
“我抛下了我的孩子”
I've abandoned my child!
“我竟然抛下了我的儿子啊”
I've abandoned my boy!
周六夜现场小品《玩具广告》
蒙太奇字幕组 原创译制
字幕贡献者
翻译/时间轴：小p
合成：
蒙太奇字幕组 (MontageSubs)
用爱发电 ♥ Powered by Love